keyforgegame.com 2019-12-20

# Privacy Policy

Fantasy Flight Games, a division of Asmodee North America, Inc., is committed to protecting your privacy. Asmodee North America, Inc is located at 1995 County Rd B2 W, 55113 Roseville, MN. Asmodee North America is a subsidiary of the Asmodee group. This privacy policy applies to the FFG Website and governs data collection and usage at all FFG Website services; it does not apply to other online or offline sites, products or services. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described below.

## Collection of your Personal Information

As an e-commerce and community website, FFG collects personal information, such as but not limited to your e-mail address, name, home or work address and/or telephone number.

## Use of your Personal Information General

Personal information collected by FFG from an Online Store Account (see Terms for definition) is used for the purpose of billing and shipping your online purchases.

Personal information collected by FFG from a Player Account, including, but not limited to, the zip code and games lists, is used for community and geographical search functions and product use data compilation.

FFG does not sell, rent or lease its customers’ personal information to third parties. It is possible that FFG may use personal information to inform you of other products and services available from FFG and its affiliates. FFG may also contact you via surveys or other means to conduct research about your opinion of current services or potential new services that may be offered. In those cases, your personal information is NOT released by FFG.

FFG occasionally hires other companies to provide limited services on its behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

FFG does not collect, use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

FFG may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on FFG or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of FFG, including its web site; or (c) act under extenuating circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the FFG Website or the public.

Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which FFG or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. FFG abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

## Control of your Personal Information

FFG offers its customers choices for the collection, use and sharing of personal information.

On the Player Account, you can opt to display or hide certain information about yourself. Certain information may be viewable by the public, and certain information may only be viewable by those you confirm as a “Friend”. Your “Friend” list, games lists and events attending will always be publicly viewable and searchable.

Any CCs (please see the Accounts section in the Terms for definition of CCs) between you and FFG or any other user are not confidential, and FFG cannot be and is not responsible for maintaining any sort of confidentiality of CCs.

## Unsubscribing from Announcements – Opt-out Policy

From time to time, we send announcements by e-mail: news about coming games, important changes in our Site or Services, special offers, etc. You may choose to completely turn off these announcements at any time by going to [your profile](https://account.asmodee.net/en/profile) and update the "I agree to receive newsletters and offers from Asmodee and its partners" checkbox in the Subscriptions section. If you are not logged in to your account, you may also use the [Unsubscribe page](https://account.asmodee.net/en/unsubscribe) and enter the e-mail address that you used for your Account. Please note that if you unsubscribe, you will not receive any e-mails from us at all. If you change your mind later, you may turn the announcements back on by returning to [your profile](https://account.asmodee.net/en/profile) and update the "I agree to receive newsletters and offers from Asmodee and its partners" checkbox in the Subscriptions section.

## Security of your Personal and Financial Information

FFG is committed to protecting the security of your personal and/or financial information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal and/or financial information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal and/or information you provide on computer systems with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the internet, we protect it through Authorize.net.

## Privacy Policy Questions

If you have any general questions about your Asmodee account, please contact us at : <https://asmodee.helpshift.com/a/asmodee-net/>
